www.1000fr.net presents
-==http://www.1000fr.net==- 謦靈風軟影視論壇榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用于商業用途
Sync:FRS@°²ÄÈ¸â Ììô¥ Í¼ÒÁÀ­Í¯Ò¥
-=風軟FRM字幕組=- 翻譯: mgydz 雨瀟 沒腦聰 校對: 雨瀟 時間軸: 安娜糕 圖伊拉童謠 天籟
The Escape Artist - 01x01
脫罪大師 第一季 第一集
Taxi!
出租車
Can you take me here, please?
麻煩 我要去這兒
Right, Charles, sorry about that. OK, let me fill you in on where we are.
不好意思 Charles 我給你說說進度
We had the cocaine in a holdall.
拿著裝有可卡因的旅行袋
We moved into the car park
進了停車場
where we saw our friend Mr Scott walking out from behind his van
看到Scott先生從他車后走出來
holding a double-barrelled shotgun.
舉著把雙筒獵槍
OK, listen, see you in about an hour.
好了 聽著 一小時后見
OK. OK, bye.
嗯 挂了
Sorry about that. I'm a lawyer.
抱歉嚇到你 我是律師
Honestly.
真的
Jamie's dad, Mr Burton, has come in today to talk about what he does at work.
Jamie的爸爸Burton先生 今天來為大家講講他的職業
Do any of you know what a barrister does? Yes, Jamie?
有人了解大律師嗎 Jamie請說
He stops people from going to prison.
他幫人不用坐牢
And how does he do that?
怎么做到的呢
He tells a court that someone didn't do a crime.
上庭說明那人沒犯罪
And sometimes the evidence doesn't cut it.
有時証據不足
And sometimes that means he can't come on holiday like he promised.
有時他可能沒法如約陪我過節了
Actually, my job is mostly standing up and talking to a judge in court.
其實我主要是起立跟法官交談
What do you talk about?
談什么呢
If someone said they saw you take your classmate's pen,
有人說看到你拿了同學的筆
and you said you didn't,
但你說沒拿
my job would be to show that whoever saw you was mistaken.
那我就証明指証你的人錯了
What happens if I did take the pen anyway?
要是我真拿了筆呢
Well, then you'd be guilty.
那你就有罪了啊
Yeah, but what if I said I didn't take it,
嗯 如果我堅持說沒拿呢
and the person who saw me has bad eyesight,
指証我的人視力不好
and you're so good at arguing they can't be sure it was me who took it?
你能言善辯 他們不能肯定是我拿的
Ah! Well, then, that's what you call a reasonable doubt.
這個嘛 就叫合理疑點
So I get to keep the pen?
那我能留著筆了?
Yes, but then you'd be getting away with it.
嗯 你蒙混過關了
Only if your dad was on my side.
前提是你爸站在我這邊
- Hi, Charles. - Will.
- 嗨 Charles - Will
Are we ready?
准備好了嗎
Crown called. Seems Maggie Gardner's stepping in as lead junior.
檢方打來過 說是Maggie Gardner 作為主控官參與此案
Again?
又來?
Surprised she could squeeze in a case between TV appearances.
沒想到她除了上電視還有空搞案子
Suppose I'm flattered.
我真是榮幸之至啊
It's like a derby match with you. They should sell tickets.
就跟你倆打德比似的 該賣票啊
It was the only object Mr Kumarin had to hand.
Kumarin先生手上只有這個
A hunting knife is not a defensive weapon! The clue is in the name.
獵刀并非防御武器 聽名字就知道
- Miss Gardner. - I apologise, My Lord.
- Gardner小姐 - 抱歉 法官大人
A man about to be attacked does not have to wait for permission.
將受攻擊的人不必等許可
The law tells us, in the right circumstances, a pre-emptive strike is justified.
法律里說在一定情況下 先發制人是合理的
In this case, a loaded shotgun aimed squarely at his head!
本案中上膛獵槍直指他的頭
We only have Mr Scott's appalling aim to thank that Mr Kumarin is here
幸好Scott先生的槍法奇爛 Kumarin先生才能現身法庭
and not being scraped off the nightclub wall with a trowel.
而不是葬身夜總會門外
Well done, Will.
干得漂亮 Will
Mr Will, thank you very much.
Will先生 太謝謝你了
- Pleasure. Take care. - Thank you.
- 客氣 保重 - 謝謝
"Police continue to make headway in their investigation
Sandra Mullen慘死一案
into the brutal murder of Sandra Mullen,
警方偵查工作不斷有新進展
acting on new evidence that has come to light in the past few days.
正調查這几天出現的新証據
Detectives are still calling for witnesses
警方仍號召目擊者
to come forward with any additional information they may have
關于Mullen慘遭儀式性殺害
concerning the ritualistic slaying of Miss Mullen,
若有信息請主動上報
whose tortured body was found on heathland
去年十月有人在郊外遛狗時發現死者
by a dog walker last October.
尸體傷痕累累
Miss Mullen, who was 25 at the time of her death
Mullen小姐 死時年僅25歲
and studying to be a doctor,
醫科在讀
was last seen leaving a night club in the early hours of Thursday morning."
最后是周四清晨在一家夜店露面
No, thank you, we have insulation!
謝謝不用了 這里隔離了
We have a warrant to conduct a search of these premises!
我們有搜查令查這里
Come back after breakfast!
早餐后再來
Mr Foyle!
Foyle先生
After breakfast!!
說了早餐后
- Well-played. - Thank you.
- 表現真好 - 謝謝夸獎
- How's life? - Ah, pleasure and pain.
- 最近如何 - 有苦有甜
Oh, Kate saw you on Loose Women the other day.
Kate有看到你上Loose Women節目呢
- You're playing it very cool. - Cool?
- 你裝什么淡定啊 - 淡定?
This... This whole Top 40 nonsense.
律師榜單什么的
- What are you talking about? - You haven't heard?
- 你說什么呢 - 你沒聽說嗎
Oh, false modesty!
裝什么謙虛
It's so unappealing, Will.
真討厭 Will
I don't know what you're talking about.
完全不曉得你說什么
We've never had a number one. Congratulations.
我們還沒出過第一呢 恭喜你
Ah. You'd heard already?
你已經聽說了?
Er, no, but that explains the
沒 這下我懂了
*** warm welcome outside the robing room.
(第一名 William Burton) 一出更衣室的熱烈歡迎
I don't think it's limited to there.
(第二名 Margaret Gardner) 我看還不止如此呢
Well done, Mr Burton. That's silk now for you, surely?
厲害啊 Burton先生 該升御用大律師了
If you say so, Mr Monk.
過獎了 Monk先生
You fill out the application, I'll buy a stamp. How's that?
你填申請表 我買郵票 怎樣
- Don't do this to me! - You should consider it.
- 別這樣對我啊 - 你該考慮考慮
Don't stay a junior all your life, hm?
總不能做一輩子普通大律師吧
Well, Harris can, but that's red brick education for you.
Harris能 但你是名牌大學出來的啊
I like getting my hands dirty.
我可不喜歡閑著
Ah, but you're different, Will. So very... special.
你不一樣啊 Will 你獨樹一幟
Bonus prize.
額外獎勵 Burton先生
No, we're actually up to the cottage for the weekend.
不行 我們周末要去郊區別墅度假
Read that, will you?
看一下吧
Knowing you it shouldn't take long.
你速度很快的
We're out of mobile range. Very unfortunate. Tragic, in fact.
那兒沒信號 真不幸 悲劇啊
Simkins Brown asked for you.
Simkins Brown點名要你
- Personally. - Really?
- 欽點啊 - 是嗎
Although I'd keep that particular factoid to yourself if I were you.
要是我肯定把這事兒保密
They asked for you over any of the silks.
人家不要御用大律師 就要你
Can't say I blame them.
這也不能怪人家
If I was in their client's shoes, I'd want your record on my side.
我要是站在他委托人的立場 也想找有不敗記錄的律師
If you're chained up in a safe at the bottom of a shark tank,
你要被鎖在鯊魚池底
you don't call for Paul Daniels.
誰會找喜劇魔朮師
You call for Houdini.
肯定找逃生魔朮師吧
Come on.
快點
Nice one. Good pass. Good pass! Come on!
漂亮 傳得好 傳得好 加把勁
There we go, now we're talking.
這就對了嘛
Come on. Keep an eye on the ball!
喂 盯住球啊
Here we... Oh, come on, referee!
很好 我靠 裁判
Grow a sac, for God's sake!
有種點行不行啊
- Potatoes, she means sack of potatoes. - You're here!
- 土豆 她說種土豆呢 - 你來了
Oh, God... Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
天啊 射門 射門 射啊
Oh, wee man.
小家伙
I found an apple in my jacket this morning.
早上我在外套里找到個蘋果
I was sending you a message - through the medium of fruit.
我借水果給你暗示呢
- The message being? - Eat fruit.
- 暗示什么 - 多吃水果
- You don't think I'm getting my five a day? - No.
- 你覺得我沒一天五蔬果嘛? - 嗯
I don't think you're eating anything that isn't made from cheese.
我覺得你不吃非奶酪制品
I think you'll find you have to press the button first.
還以為你能摸索出要先按按鈕
I did press it. I used a pressing motion.
按了啊 認真按了一下好嘛
There now.
這樣啦
- I just did that. - OK.
- 我按怎么沒反應 - 行啦
Thanks for your support. Really appreciate it.
謝謝幫助 超感激的
Come on, we're going.
快點 要走了
Yeah.
來了
Hang on.
等一下
Get your bags off the back seat. OK?
包別忘了拿啊
- Hey, Ben. - All right.
- 嘿 Ben - 嗨
You're the Pied Piper of bubble baths.
你真是泡泡浴小王后
You know, there might be room in here for a large Scotsman.
這浴缸來個大男人也坐得下
- I've got to catch up on something. - Oh, well, suit yourself.
- 我還有活兒要趕 - 那隨便你了
It's all candles and twilight in here though.
這兒可浪漫了 燭光伴黃昏
Your loss.
不來你損失
Stop snoring.
別打呼了
Sorry, am I keeping you up?
抱歉 弄醒你了啊
Funny guy. Hmm...
你好可愛
You were quite the hit at school yesterday. So Jamie said.
Jamie說你昨天在學校很受歡迎
They seemed to enjoy it.
他們好像挺愛聽的
All his wee pals want you to be their lawyer now.
他的小伙伴都想找你當律師了
They're all going to go out and commit GBH safe in the knowledge you'll get them off.
都計划搞些大破壞 反正你能幫他們脫罪
Well, that's very reassuring.
真寬慰啊
Little do they know that that large brain of yours is full of holes.
他們都不知道你早傷透腦筋了
Your hard drive's full.
你滿負荷了
- That's your problem. - I see.
- 知不知道 - 我知道
You just need to back it up now and again.
你得時不時放松一下
How do I do that?
怎么個放松法
Well...
這個嘛
Mmm. You're so nice and warm.
你真是美好又溫暖
Mr Simkins, why did you choose me to lead this?
Simkins先生 為什么選我來主打?
I mean, why me, over a silk?
為什么選我 不選御用大律師
Because I've seen too many silks who try and
因為我見過太多御用大律師
waltz in and blunderbuss their way through a case they've only glanced at on the way to the court.
在上庭的路上瞄一眼案子 就隨隨便便去打官司了
Because in a case like this I want someone who spends days elbows deep in the evidence.
這種大案我希望負責律師 花上几天深入研究証據
Because my client stands between a rock and a bucket of shit
我的委托人正進退兩難
and he needs all the help he can get.
不容有任何閃失
And?
所以呢
- Honestly? - Yeah.
- 說實話嗎 - 當然
Hmph. Because you win.
因為你百戰百勝
Are you sleeping here now, Mr Burton?
你是睡這兒了嗎 Burton先生
What time is it?
什么時間了
Tuesday.
禮拜二
I think I fancy Carlos Tevez.
我比較喜歡特維斯
For captain.
來當隊長
Did you look at these pictures?
你看過這些照片了嗎
You ever seen anything like it?
見過這樣的嗎
Before?
以前
I've never.
我從來沒有
She was alive for most of it, you know?
她几乎是被活活虐死的
She was alive.
活活虐死
"We were walking through the park, listening to music on our iPod.
"走過公園 iPod里放著歌"
We did not notice the blood on our shoes until we got home.
"直到回家才發現鞋上的血跡"
Because we'd not been paying much attention to where we'd been walking,
"走的時候沒注意地上"
and our walk had taken us through areas of deeper undergrowth and high grasses.
"因為穿過了深深的草叢"
When we first saw the blood we presumed we had stepped in the remains of an animal."
"見到血跡還以為是踩了動物尸體"
A squirrel, for example?
比如說小松鼠
Yes.
沒錯
Did you know the grey squirrels are killing all the red squirrels?
你知道灰松鼠會殺紅松鼠嗎
I did, yes.
知道
But now they've discovered a black squirrel.
現在還發現了黑松鼠
Mr Foyle.
Foyle先生
And that's killing all the greys.
它們殺灰松鼠
Goes to show, you can't be too careful.
所以說你得慎之又慎
Mr Foyle. Can we please get on?
Foyle先生 能說正事嗎
What day do you take your laundry to be service washed, Mr Foyle?
你一般哪天把衣服送去洗的 Foyle先生
Tuesday's wash day.
禮拜二是洗衣日
Can you explain why, after months of Tuesdays, you took your washing in on a Monday?
几個月來都是周二洗 為什么突然換到周一
We'd run out of pants, hadn't we?
總有褲子不夠穿的時候
We took our laundry to be washed a day early because we'd run out of clothing.
提前一天去洗衣店是因為沒衣服穿了
- Correct. - The fact we found blood on our shoes after our walk
- 正是 - 散步后鞋上沾到血跡
increased our desire to do our washing early.
更讓人想提前洗衣服
That's the truth.
說得沒錯
Do you normally wash your shoes in the washing machine?
你會拿洗衣機洗鞋子嗎
I do if they have blood on them.
沾了血當然會啊
Right.
好
Erm... We're going to have to talk about the websites.
呃 還要聊聊上網的事
The other side are going to try to claim you habitually view images and video
對方會說你習慣看那些
that are commonly referred to as "extreme pornography",
大家稱為"極端色情"的視頻或照片
an umbrella term for filmed acts which threaten, or appear to threaten, a person's life,
泛指那些威脅或表現威脅人生安全
result in serious injury to participants or appear to involve torture, biting,
導致參與者嚴重受傷 或是表現蹂躪啃咬
sexual interference with a human corpse.
甚至與尸體性交的影片
And that this has a link to the nature of the injuries sustained by the victim.
這與死者身上的傷息息相關
I don't do that kind of thing.
我不做那種事
Unfortunately, your credit card statements tell a different story.
可惜你的信用卡賬單不這么說
They show payments to a number of websites, which have been revealed to distribute this...
里面有線上消費 而這些網站被曝光散播...
this kind of material.
此類影片
The credit cards are lying.
賬單不屬實
Right.
好吧
I have to tell you, Mr Foyle, already this is a huge challenge.
我得說 Foyle先生 這已經是個大挑戰了
We're going to have to work on your presentation style.
你的陳述技巧得好好改改
What you see is what you get.
所見即所得
Yes, well, that's part of the problem, isn't it?
這就是個問題啊
- Does he have to be here? - Yes, he does. Yeah.
- 他非得在場嗎 - 對 必須在
Here's the thing, Mr Burton,
是這樣的 Burton先生
and I don't know whether you've picked it up
不知道你發沒發現
or perhaps your sixth sense might have spotted it.
或者有沒有意識到
I don't like people very much.
我不太愛跟人打交道
I'm just not a very nice person.
我不太好相處
I'm not here to judge you.
我不是來評判你的
No, the man in red does that.
但法官會評判我
I'm here to defend you and present your case as best as I can.
我是來為你辯護 盡力為你打官司的
In order to do that... You think I did it, don't you?
- 要打贏... - 你覺得是我做的吧
- That's the problem. - It's not what I was saying.
- 這就是問題了 - 我沒這么說
You think I did all those awful things to that poor woman.
你覺得是我折磨了那可憐的女人
- ??Listen to me. - I don't think I will.
- Foyle先生 請聽我說 - 不必了
Mr Foyle.
Foyle先生
I want him gone.
讓他走人
He's your solicitor.
他是你的事務律師
Gone.
滾蛋
He was making me nervous.
他讓我緊張了
Do you want to take a minute?
要休息一下嗎
Staring at me.
他盯著我
- Mr Foyle. - Look me in the eye.
- Foyle先生 - 看著我
Shall we get on?
可以繼續了嗎
How about a nice cup of tea?
來杯茶怎么樣
Mr Foyle, I'm your defence barrister.
Foyle先生 我是你的辯護律師
If you privately confessed your guilt to me in any way
如果你私下向我承認罪行
but publicly maintained your innocence,
公開卻堅持自己清白
I'd be following Mr Simkins there,
我就跟Simkins先生一起走了
and I would have encouraged you as I left to enter a guilty plea.
我會鼓勵你進行有罪答辯
I'm not guilty.
我沒有罪
Then this is where we are.
那我們就照你說的來辦
Well, good job you're here then.
幸好有你在
- Refreshing. - Let's hope so.
- 讓人精神一振 - 但愿如此
Your manners.
我是說你的儀態
- Full? - Just a splash.
- 倒滿嗎 - 一點就好
You know, it's funny.
有意思的是
The more time we spend together,
我們接觸的時間越長
the more you remind me of me.
你就越讓我想起自己
Right.
是嗎
- Mr Burton? - Give me a minute.
- Burton先生 - 讓我緩緩
-Are you all right? - I just need some air.
- 你還好嗎 - 只是需要透透氣
- Can I have 20 Marlboro Lights, please? - Yep.
- 能麻煩給我包特醇萬寶路嗎 - 好的
- And a lighter if you have got one. - Sure.
- 有打火機的話也要一個 - 沒問題
Ah, here she is, the rising star at 57 Harlow Street.
她來了 Harlow街57號冉冉升起的新星
Now then, Maggie, I know I should really be rooting for you
Maggie 我知道我該毫無保留地支持你
without exception, but you should know there is no ignominy in coming second.
但是要知道位列第二也不是什么丟人的事
Just ask Buzz Aldrin.
好比Buzz Aldrin (繼阿姆斯特朗之后登上月球第二人)
Well, I demand a recount.
我要求重新統計結果
Takes me back to Middle Temple Moot Finals.
讓我想起中殿法學院的模擬仲裁庭決賽
- Really? - Yeah, you and me. Almost an exact replay.
- 真的嗎 - 是啊 你和我 往事重演啊
It was a long time ago.
很久之前的事了
I heard you're up against our boy Julian on this Liam Foyle malarkey.
聽說這個Liam Foyle的案子 你要對付的是咱們的Julian
Is that so? Our boy?
是嗎 我們的人?
Yes. Surprised it's not you on the other side.
是啊 對手竟然不是你
Seem to be making a habit out of it.
都有點不習慣了
Thought I'd give you a go against someone else for a change.
想給你個機會和別人過過招嘛
Had enough, eh?
受夠了 對吧
Never.
永遠不會
I am just thinking of transitioning into more defence work.
我只是做些改變 多接些辯護的案子
- Excuse me. - Sure.
- 失陪了 - 好的
Anyway, this Foyle case is a little too St Jude for my liking.
再說了 Foyle的案子對我來說 也太小菜一碟了
He's the patron saint of lost causes.
他必輸無疑
Oh, I didn't know that.
這可說不准
Right, well, I'll go and get us some more rubbing alcohol.
好了 我再去給咱倒點酒
Great, thank you.
好的 謝謝
I'm serious. I've seen the brief. Why are you doing?
說真的 我看過案卷 你為什么要接
I'm practising law.
我在盡律師的職責
Oh, come on. It's almost a no-questions jobbie.
少來了 這就是個板上釘釘的案子
It might be exposure but for all the wrong reasons.
也許會有曝光率 但不會光彩
I don't do things for exposure, Maggie.
我做事不是為了曝光率 Maggie
Why do you do it?
那是為了什么
Because everyone deserves a defence.
因為每個人都享有辯護的權利
There you go.
吹吧
Yeah!
好棒
- Make a wish.Yes. - I wish my mum would stop annoying me.
- 許個愿 - 我希望我媽別來煩我了
- Who wants a piece of cake? - Me!
- 誰要來片蛋糕 - 我
- Are you sure? - Yes!
- 確定嗎 - 是的
OK, so you're saying there's more to find?
好的 你是說還有其他的發現?
Yeah. And would you go on record with that?
是的 你能出庭作証嗎
Great. Great, OK. Someone from my office will call you tomorrow and set up an appointment.
好的 好的 明天我辦公室的人 會給你打電話約時間的
Thanks. Thank you. Speak soon. Bye-bye.
謝謝你 保持聯系 再見
Who was that?
是誰的電話
That's a clever man who knows about computers.
是一個懂電腦的聰明人
Is he going to back up your brain?
他要備份你的記憶嗎
No, it was for my work.
不是 是工作上的事
Will he help you win the case?
他會幫你打贏官司嗎
I hope so.
但愿如此
Yeah. Mmm...
好了
Oh, here they come.
他們來了
How's Kate and the family?
Kate和家里人還好嗎
Very well, thank you.
很好 謝謝
I think Maggie's in the gallery today.
我想Maggie今天來旁聽
Why's she doing that?
為什么
Checking out the competition I expect.
來看好戲的吧
That's the trouble with being number one.
第一名的麻煩就在這
Everyone wants to knock you off your perch.
所有人都想讓你認輸
Now I heard you asked for an adjournment last week.
我聽說你上周要求延期
I did indeed. Trouble at t'mill?
- 是的 - 碰上問題了嗎
- Not really. Just needed more time. - Well, here we are, I'm afraid.
- 倒沒有 只是需要多點時間 - 恐怕時間到了
Here we are indeed.
沒錯 時間到了
I must say, I do like your game face, old boy.
我得說我很喜歡你迎戰的表情 老伙計
You haven't seen it yet, old boy.
這還不是呢 老伙計
Some crimes defy description.
有些惡行令人發指得難以言表
They debase our so-called civilisation and defy every boundary of humanity left to us.
貶低了所謂的文明 并且蔑視人性的底線
Now the person who took the life of Sandra Mullins
奪去Sandra Mullins生命的人
can only be described as a malignant sadist,
只能用喪心病狂的虐待狂來形容
who did so with the intent to traumatise, to terrorise,
旨在蓄意傷害 恐嚇
and to inflict the maximum amount of pain and suffering.
以及最大程度的給受害人帶來疼痛和煎熬
And we intend to prove, without doubt, that that person was Liam Foyle.
而我們要証明 這個人毫無疑問就是Liam Foyle
Severe bruising around her neck,
她的脖子周圍有嚴重的淤青
her thyroid cartilage and hyoid bone were badly fractured.
她的甲狀軟骨和舌骨嚴重骨折
Cause of death was strangulation.
死亡的原因是窒息
Other injuries were sexual in nature,
其他的傷是性侵犯所致
internal and external,
內外傷都有
both eyes were missing,
雙眼都不見了
removed with force close to the time of death, possibly before.
是在接近死亡時間被取走的 可能是在死亡前
The park gets overgrown towards the north eastern corner.
公園的東北角雜草叢生
Long grass, hawthorn, lavender, nettle beds.
長得很高的野草 山楂 薰衣草   麻草叢
And did you see anything unusual on your morning route?
你早晨經過有看到什么不尋常的事情嗎
I saw a man.
我看見了一個男人
Getting up from a lying position.
先是躺著然后站了起來
Mr Hughes, in your professional capacity,
Hughes先生 憑借你的專業能力
can you please confirm the credit card statements before you are
你能確認在你面前的這張信用卡
an accurate reflection of payments made by your bank
能准地反映出Liam Foyle先生
- on behalf of the account holder, Mr Liam Foyle? - Yes.
- 通過你們銀行進行的支付嗎 - 是的
- And these payments were made by the card over the first three months of this year, is that correct? - Yes.
- 而且這些支付是在今年前三個月完成的 對嗎
And they were all made online to companies across Asia and Europe,
并且它們都是在網上支付給 橫跨亞歐的公司
all of which distribute and produce the same... product,
這些公司傳播和制造同樣的...產品
namely pornography, is that correct?
也就是色情出版物 對嗎
Yes, that is our understanding.
在我們看來是這樣的
Mr Hughes, many of these sites, and I'm afraid we have had to visit them
Hughes先生 這些網站中的大部分 在這次的調查當中 我們不得已
in the course of this investigation,
進入這些網站發現
have shown acts of extreme depravity which,
有一些極端惡劣的場面
we understand from the forensic reports,
而通過驗尸報告我們認為
show disturbingly accurate similarities to the injuries
這些手段與Sandra Mulins被謀殺前
that befell Sandra Mullins before she was murdered.
所被傷害的方式有驚人的吻合
I talk specifically in relation to the bite marks
這里具體指的是咬痕
and the mutilation of genitalia.
以及外陰部位的傷痕
Liar!
騙子
Mr Foyle! You have one chance with me, and that was it.
Foyle先生 這是你最后一次機會
Any more from you and I shall hold you in contempt.
再說話我就視為蔑視法庭
Murderer! Silence, please!
- 凶手 - 請肅靜
Mr Hughes, please answer the question.
Hughes先生 請回答問題
Yes, it is the same card.
沒錯 是同一張卡
Thank you. No further questions, My Lord.
(暴民) 謝謝你 問題問完了 法官大人
Mr Burton?
Burton先生
My Lord, before this trial began I made a written application for an adjournment.
法官大人 開庭之前我遞交了 延緩開庭的書面請求
I'm asking you now to reconsider that application in the light of the gravity of the expert testimony.
由于專家証詞分量 現在我請求您 再次考慮這個請求
Oh, come on.
不是吧
??This is most inappropriate.
Burton先生 這樣很不恰當
??An adjournment will bring vital evidence to light.
休庭后將呈上關鍵証據
Let both sides have their expert, and let the jury decide.
雙方都請出專家 讓陪審團做決定
Mr Burton,there is huge public interest in having this case heard as soon as possible.
Burton先生 盡快審理本案關系到公眾利益
The fact your expert has not mustered himself to the task at hand is neither here nor there.
與你的專家能不能准時趕到沒有關系
He's not slow, he's gathering potentially new evidence.
他并不是慢 而是在收集潛在的新証據
It's the same computer.
都是同一台電腦
Both of your experts are computer forensic specialists.
你們雙方的專家都是計算機取証的專家
I can hardly see how two trained men looking at the same equipment
我看不出兩個專業人士檢查同一台設備
could produce so radically different conclusions that it would make a difference.
能得出有怎樣天壤之別的結論
I'm afraid it simply isn't on.
恐怕沒有差別吧
I think if My Lord could look a little closer...
如果法官大人能再考慮...
Your application was refused and it shall stay refused.
你的請求被拒絕了 沒有商量的余地
I will decline from pursuing you on contempt
我不追究你蔑視法庭
but let this be your last and final warning.
但這是你最后的警告
We'll break for lunch now -
現在是午休時間
but the train is on the tracks, Mr Burton.
但一切照常進行 Burton
And for the sake of your client I suggest you deal with it.
為了你的委托人 我建議你看著辦
My Lord.
是的 法官大人
- All rise. - Choo-choo.
全體起立
Will?
Will?
You should try and sleep.
你該試著去睡會兒的
- I'm fine. - I mean it.
- 我沒事 - 說真的
You think you're invincible, and you're not.
你覺得自己堅不可摧 不是的
We should get new locks on these windows.
我們該給這些窗戶換新鎖
Were you even listening to me?
你在聽我說的話嗎
Frame locks, with keys.
框架鎖 配鑰匙的那種
Oh, God. You're going to drive me crazy for the next two months now, aren't you?
天啊 接下來的兩個月 你要把我逼瘋對吧
A colleague of mine just defended a 12-year-old boy who poured drain cleaner down the throat of his best mate
我的一個同事剛為一個12歲的男孩辯護 他把潔廁劑倒進了他最好朋友的喉嚨里
because he wouldn't let him play a game on his phone.
因為朋友不讓他用手機玩游戲
The world is broken.
世風日下
You shouldn't watch scary movies so close to bedtime.
你不該睡覺前看恐怖電影
Yeah.
是啊
Not inspiring much confidence up there, Will.
法庭上的表現沒什么信心啊 Will
- I know what I'm doing, Mr Foyle. - Not from where I'm sitting.
- 我知道自己在做什么 Foyle先生 - 我可沒看出來
So sack me. Why would I want to do that?
- 那就解雇我 - 我為什么要這么做
You tell me. I work for you as long as you'll have me.
你說呢 你雇了我 我就會為你工作
I apologise, Will. I know you've got my back.
我道歉 Will 我知道你是在幫我
I appreciate your honesty very much.
我很感激你的真誠
Shall we get on?
我們要繼續嗎
You only have one computer, is that correct?
你只有一台電腦 對嗎
Yes. But I don't see what that's got to do with what happened to that woman.
是的 但我不明白 這和那個女士的遭遇有什么關系
You will.
你會明白的
Someone must pay for what happened to Sandra Mullins.
一定要有人對Sandra Mullins的事負責
Our very humanity is at stake, as my learned friend has indicated.
正如對方律師所說 我們的人性收到了威脅
It would be convenient
對于今天在坐的每一位來說
for everyone here today If Liam Foyle was guilty.
如果Liam Foyle有罪 事情就很好辦
The cuffs go on and he's gone forever.
給他銬上手銬 就再也見不到他了
The evidence seems overwhelming.
証據似乎已經確鑿
But it is not.
但并非如此
We may dislike Mr Foyle.
我們也許并不喜歡Foyle先生
We might cross the street if we saw him coming.
我們見到他也許都會繞道
But we do not have to like him to defend him.
但我們為他辯護并不需要喜歡他
Because this is not a popularity contest, this is not a witch-Hunt,
因為這不是比誰受歡迎 不是莫須有的迫害
This is a court of law,
這里是法庭
And in this country, when you're accused of a crime
而在這個國家 當有人被指控犯罪時
You are presumed to be innocent until proven guilty.
在被証實有罪之前 都是清白的
And make no mistake, not a shred of what you've heard from
要知道 你們從控方律師那里
My learned friend acting for the Prosecution
聽到的指控
Has given any proof at all.
并沒有給出任何証據
I will show you unreliable witnesses,
讓我一一指出這些不可靠的目擊者
Lazy forensic science,
懶散的法醫
Emotional appeals instead of factual accuracies.
情感上有煽動力卻不能說明事實
Oh, yes, and the casual assertion that my client
對了 還有隨意斷言我的委托人
is a consumer of extreme pornography.
是極端色情出版物的消費者
First, I think, we will talk about that.
首先 我們來說說這個
I am an expert in forensic computer data analysis.
我是警方計算機數據分析的專家
Dr Crowe, have you had a chance to examine the hard drive
Crowe博士 你檢驗過
of the computer belonging to Mr Foyle?
Foyle先生的計算機硬盤了嗎
Yes, I have.
是的 檢驗過了
And you did this instructed by the Prosecution in this case, is that correct?
你是按照本案控方的指示檢驗的 對嗎
Yes.
是的
Unfortunately Dr Weeks,
遺憾的是 Weeks博士
the gentleman who has helped examine the computer for the Defence
這位協助辯方檢驗計算機的先生
Has not yet finished his work.
還沒完成他的工作
However, he has passed me his notes to date
但他給我了目前為止的記錄
and I'd like to ask you questions about them.
我想向你請教一些有關的問題
Wherever you go on the internet, using a computer,
無論用電腦上什么網
- You leave footprints. Is that correct? - Yes, it is.
- 都會留下痕跡 對嗎 - 是的 沒錯
Even if you've deleted a file, someone like you is able to see it.
即便刪除了檔案 像你這樣的專家還是能找到痕跡
- Most of the time. - Where is this going?
- 大多數情況下可以 - 你想說什么
In the absence of my own expert,
在我方專家缺席的情況下
My learned friend has kindly tendered the Prosecution expert on this matter.
對方律師好心地讓控方專家來幫忙
I beg some time to explore this point with him.
我請求能有多些時間和他討這個問題
Very well.
好的
My learned friend alleges that my client paid for and viewed,
對方律師宣稱我的委托人經常
On a regular basis,
支付并且觀看
Numerous depraved and abusive images, including...
許多內容惡劣以及虐待的圖片 包括
"Acts of torture, mutilation, strangulation, and necrophilia."
"折磨 截肢 勒頸和奸尸"
Um, in your analysis of his computer,
在你檢驗他電腦的過程中
Did you establish that Mr Foyle
你能否証實Foyle先生
Had actually visited ANY of those websites
真正訪問過上述任何一個
that Pertained to those images?
含有所述圖片的網站
- No, but his credit card bills... - Thank you.
- 沒有 但是他的信用卡賬單... - 謝謝
And my learned friend asserted that my client paid for access
而對方律師聲稱我的委托人
To many of those websites with his credit card.
用信用卡付費進入上述網站
Now,
那么
Why would he pay for them if he didn't actually visit them?
他如果不上這些網站 又為什么要付錢呢
It may sound reprehensible but he's not getting his money's worth, is he?
這么說也許不大好 但他錢花的并不值 不是嗎
How did he pay for access to those sites without actually visiting them?
沒有真正訪問這些網站又怎么付費呢
Many porn sites were on his internet history
他的上網記錄中有許多色情網站
To which he submitted his credit card details.
他向這些網站提供了信用卡信息
That's how he received a password to unlock other content elsewhere.
這樣他就得到了在別處解鎖其他內容的密碼
Is it possible that his card details were falsified at that point?
他的信用卡信息可能是偽造的嗎
How do you mean?
你指的是什么
That when he submitted his details to the adult site,
當他向成人網站提供他的信息時
They were taken and used by unknown third parties
被未知的第三方拿去用于
To pay for and unlock this "other content" as you call it.
支付和解鎖你所說的"其他內容"
Is that possible?
有這種可能嗎
I suppose so, yes.
我想是有的
So given this possibility, if we were to prove, in this court,
鑒于這種可能性 如果我們能在法庭上証實
That such falsification occurred, would Mr Foyle be shown to be,
存在有偽造信息 那么Foyle先生
In fact, a victim of identity fraud?
實際上就成了身份欺詐的受害人
This is not a trial about extreme pornography,
法官大人 這不是在審判極端色情
This is about the horrific murder...
而是在審判殘忍的謀殺
Our expert was in the process of proving this link.
我方專家之前在証明其中的聯系
Hence our application for an adjournment, which was refused.
因此我方提出延期 而請求被駁回
My learned friend brought these hideous allegations to bear on this case
針對對方律師就此案 提出的這些令人發指的指控
and I reiterate my request.
我重申延期的請求
The expert testimony cuts both ways.
雙方都應該有專家証詞
Usher, please excuse the jury.
法警 請陪審團退席
A matter of procedure has just arisen,
出現了程序問題
I need to talk to both sides about it.
我得和雙方談談
We will call you back presently.
稍后會請你們回來
My room, I think.
去我辦公室吧
My client has been falsely branded an extreme porn enthusiast by the Crown,
法官大人 我的委托人被檢方 錯誤地打上了色情狂的烙印
This has now leaked online to social media,
這已經泄露到網上的社交媒體了
where it's been duly picked up by the print media,
然后又適時被平面媒體發掘
Which has now tainted my client with the label torturer, pervert, necrophiliac,
導致我的委托人名聲受損 被貼上虐待狂 性變態及戀尸癖的標簽
So much so this jury must be discharged and a new jury called.
因此這批陪審團必須解散 并召集新的陪審團
Even with the reporting restrictions,
即便有報道限制
Given the press this case has already generated,
考慮到本案已有的輿論傾向
Mr Foyle cannot be given a fair trial.
Foyle無法得到公正的審判
The application is to stay the indictment.
我只能申請停止訴訟
- This is absurd. - I made the request in good time.
- 太荒唐了 - 我的請求很適時
Yes, I know.
是的 我明白
The prejudice to the accused In the eyes of this jury is, in my view, permanent.
在我看來 陪審團對被告的偏見 是難以更改的
Reluctantly, I feel that I have little option in these circumstances
雖然很不情愿 但我感到 在此情況下 我別無選擇
- But to accede to your application. - Judge, please.
- 只能同意你的申請 - 法官大人 拜托
I ballsed up, Julian.
我搞糟了 Julian
I'm sorry. Let's get this over with.
抱歉 我們快點完事吧
And so, as a result, I have no alternative
因此 我別無他法
But to discharge the jury and release the defendant.
只能解散陪審團 釋放被告
All rise.
全體起立
He's got away with murder. He's got blood on his hands.
他逃脫法律制裁了 他雙手沾滿鮮血
You should be ashamed of yourself!
你應該感到羞愧
Congratulations, well done.
恭喜 干得漂亮
It was a mistake. I just made sure they paid for it.
他們犯了錯 我只是讓他們為此付出代價
Will, good man.
Will 你真是好人
- Just doing my job. - Thank you, my friend.
- 盡我的職責罷了 - 謝謝 我的朋友
Pleasure. Take care.
客氣 保重
- So show me again. - You do it.
- 再給我演示一遍 - 你來
OK. But don't watch me, I can't do it if you watch. I'm like a kettle.
好吧 但是別看著我 你看著我就要出錯 我就像水壺
What do you mean you're like a kettle?
什么叫像水壺
If I get this right I'll tell you. Go on.
等我搞定就告訴你 去吧
OK.
好吧
- "When buying clothing to say what you want, use... - Gostaria."
- 買衣服時 '要買'怎么說 - (葡萄牙語)Gostaria
Gostaria.
Gostaria
- "I'd like a shirt. - Gostaria uma camisa."
- 我要買襯衫 - Gostaria uma camisa
Gostaria uma camisa.
Gostaria uma camisa
- "I'd like a pair of trousers. - Gostaria umas calcas."
- 我要買褲子 - Gostaria umas calcas
What?
啥?
"To get the right size, use the following phrases.
"挑選尺寸時 可以用以下短語
I am a size 40."
我穿40號"
"O meu numero e quarenta."
O meu numero e quarenta
O meu numero e qua... quarenta.
O meu numero e qua... quarenta
"If they don't have the right colour, here is how to ask for the same thing in blue.
如果顏色不合適 用這句問有沒有藍色同款
Do you have this in blue?"
有藍色的嗎
Who are you waving at?
你在朝誰揮手?
I don't know.
不知道
What do you mean you don't know?
什么叫不知道?
That man. He just started waving.
那個人 是他先揮手的
What man?
哪個人
He's gone now.
已經走了
- Just go in. - "Are you peeing?"
- 進去啦 - 你在尿尿嗎
Possibly.
可能吧
Listen, just take a deep breath and open the door, You big Jessie.
聽著 深呼吸 然后推開門 別像姑娘似的
I can't. I'm scared.
不行 我好害怕
- "It's just a reunion." - Jenny said she'd be here.
- 只是同學聚會而已 - Jenny說她會來
- Who was she again? - Funny.
- 她是誰來著? - 好冷
"At least you'll have something in common."
至少你們會有共同點了
We had a deal. I can't see her anywhere.
我們說好的 我不能再見她
"You'll be fine."
沒事的啦
No, not these people. These people are all so...
跟這幫人可不會 他們太...
- Hi. - Hi, great to see you.
- 嗨 - 嗨 見到你們很高興
- Two-Faced. - "I'll tell you what.
- 兩面派 - 這樣吧
If you're still hyperventilating by the cheese course,
如果你還是緊張得呼吸急促
You can always come and see us. You know where we are.
可以來找我們啊 你知道我們在哪兒
And we're always pleased to see you.
隨時歡迎
OK. Thanks.
好吧 謝謝
I'd better go. Bye.
我得挂了 拜
- Mum. - Yes?
- 媽媽 - 怎么?
What you smiling at?
你笑什么?
It's a surprise.
有驚喜
A nice surprise.
愉快的驚喜
Come here.
過來
What's with the questions? You, you're always...
干嘛這么問 你 你老是...
Get off.
好了 好了
- So how's Edinburgh? - Still mad.
- 愛丁堡怎么樣? - 瘋狂
You should come back though.
你該回來
You get a nicer house, better schools.
有更好的房子 更好的學校
- Are you considering a career change? - I'm doing OK, thanks.
- 你在考慮轉行嗎 - 我混得還行 謝謝
I know. I read the papers.
我知道 我讀了報紙
Don't let them start without me, OK?
等我回來再開始
"And still, when winter came, he..."
等待冬季來臨 他...
Amen.
阿門
Hi.
嗨
"Where were you? I've been trying for ages."
你去哪兒了?我撥了好几通了
- What's happened? - "God, there was a man outside."
- 怎么了? - 老天 外面有個男人
I don't know, but there was somebody outside.
我說不清楚 總之外面有人
- We are at the cottage. - "Man?! What man?"
- 我們在別墅 - 男人 什么男人
I don't know what man it is!
我不知道是誰
- "There was a man, somebody!" - Kate. Kate. Breathe. Tell me again.
- 就是有個人 - Kate Kate 呼吸 再說一遍
"He was... He was at the window, and I was in the bath...
他...他在窗口 我在洗澡
He was looking in at me when I was in the bath."
我洗澡時 他從窗口看我
- How could he be at the window?! - I don't know but he was at the window!
- 他怎么會在窗戶旁邊 - 不知道 反正就是在了
Call the police, lock the doors, stay in the bedroom. OK?
打電話報警 鎖上門 呆在臥室里 明白嗎
Do not go outside. I'll be there as soon as I can. I love you, OK?
不要出去 我馬上回來 我愛你
- Did you hear me? Are you calling them? - I'm c-Calling.
- 聽到了沒有 報警了嗎 - 馬上打
Guv!
老大
Is it possible that one of your ex-Clients has a point to prove?
會不會是你以前的委托人 想要傳達什么信息?
Someone you failed to defend, perhaps did some time?
可能是以前為其辯護失敗
Well,... no.
不會的
You sound very sure.
你好像很肯定的樣子
Detective Chalmers, Mr Burton has never lost a case.
Chalmers警探 Burton從未輸過一起案子
Have you ever refused to represent someone?
你有沒有拒絕擔任誰的代理律師?
- We're not really allowed to do that. - Allowed?
- 不允許拒絕 - 不允許?
Cherry-Picking is frowned upon.
不贊成挑三揀四
Everybody's hungry.
大家都餓了 大家都餓了
Aye-Aye.
嗨
Hi. Any sign of a reply from the QC Selection Panel?
嗨 御用大律師評委會有回復了嗎
Yeah. Look, about that.
呃 聽著 是這樣的
You might want to delay a little.
恐怕得推遲一下了
- What kind of complaint? - Unprofessional conduct.
- 什么投訴 - 違反職業道德行為
He didn't come to us first?
他直接繞過我們了?
Looks like he wanted to cause you maximum discomfort.
看來他想給你制造大麻煩
Went straight to the Legal Ombudsman and the BSB. Both barrels.
直接去找了法律事務申訴專員 和律師標准委員會 火力全開
Mr Foyle asserts
Foyle先生聲稱
that you "engaged in conduct which is dishonest
你"有不正直
Or otherwise discreditable to a barrister
或有損律師名譽的行為
Contrary to paragraph 301 A1,
違背第301條A1
in particular that you expressed doubts about
具體說就是你對他辯解的正確性
The validity and honesty of his plea."
和真實性表現出質疑
What?
什么
- Is this true? - Of course not.
- 是真的嗎 - 當然不是
This is insane. We won the bloody case. We won!
簡直瘋了 我們贏了這案子 贏了啊
Looks like it's not enough.
看來光贏還不夠
What the hell's he doing?
他到底想干嘛?
Your silk application is going to have to wait till this is all sorted out.
你的御用大律師申請 得等到這調查清楚才能繼續進行
I'm sorry, it's very bad luck.
抱歉 Will 運氣真不好
We need to weigh in on this right away, stop it in its tracks.
我們得馬上介入其中 以便及時抑制發展勢頭
Enough firepower, it may well work.
有足夠火力的話 可能會起效
Danny!
Danny
See who you can rope back into the office, will you?
把人都叫回辦公室
- It's six o'clock. - Hey!
- 現在已經六點了 - 喂
We'll thrash out a strategy here and now, all right?
我們馬上研究出一套策略 好嗎
Yeah, there's been a bit of a thing at work. It's a bit weird.
工作上有點事 有點奇怪
I'm going to have to stay later but maybe we can all go up together?
我得晚點回去了 也許我們可以一起過去?
Can you hang on?
等一下
"We're ready for the off. Why don't we just see you up there, eh?
我們准備出發了 不如直接那里碰頭?
But hurry up, OK? I want to show you something."
盡快哦 我有東西給你看
- That's cryptic. - "No, not really. Oh, and listen..."
- 神神秘秘的 - 沒有啦 聽著
Oh, I am losing you.
聽不清了
- Nah. - "Hello?"
- 不 - 喂?
I'll see you later, OK?
一會兒見了 好嗎
- "Hello? Hello?" - OK.
- 喂 喂 - 好的
- We are here. Yeah, we're here. - I am really hungry.
- 到了 到了 - 我好餓
I don't care.
我不管
Listen, we are going to wait for your dad to get back so we can all eat together, OK?
聽著 等爸爸回來一起吃 好嗎
"Hi, it's Kate, I'm not here right but leave a message. Bye."
嗨 我是Kate 我現在不在 請留口訊 再見
Jamie?
Jamie?
"Try to find out if it is day or night.
"問白天還是晚上
- What are two ways to greet someone?" - "Muito prazer..."
- 兩種打招呼的方法是什么" - "Muito prazer..."
"Bom dia. Boa tarde."
"Bom dia  Boa tarde"
"Where is the nearest chemist?"
"最近的藥店在哪里?"
"Onde esta a farmacia?"
"Onde esta a farmacia?"
Kate?
Kate?
Hi.
嗨
- "There is. - Ha, sim."
- "有 - Ha sim"
Kate?
Kate?
Jamie?!
Jamie?
Kate?! Jamie?!
Kate?Jamie?
Jamie?! Jamie!!
Jamie?Jamie
Jamie!
Jamie
Oh, Jesus!
天啊
Kate!
Kate
DAD!
爸爸
- Jamie?! Jamie?! - DAD!
- Jamie?Jamie? - 爸爸
Jamie!
Jamie
Shit!
可惡
Come on!
快通啊
Yes! Police! Ambulance!
是的 警察 救護車
Words are not enough, Will.
言語無法表達 Will
Take all the time you need.
慢慢來 不著急
Chambers is a family.
律所是個大家庭
Like all families we take care of one another.
我們互相關愛
We will run with this right through to the end.
我們會負責處理到底的
- Whatever it takes. - Thank you.
- 無論要付出什么代價 - 謝謝
You have my word on it.
我保証
We'll make sure we get him.
一定會把他繩之以法
How are things?
最近怎么樣
Sorry. Shit question.
抱歉 傻問題
I'm getting through it.
會熬過去的
Sorry to call out of the blue, I was in the area.
抱歉突然打給你 我正好路過附近
It's really great that you called, Danny. I really appreciate it.
你能打來真的很好 我很感謝
- How's everything with you? - Fine, fine.
- 你們怎么樣 - 挺好的
Well, we're just...
我們...
..Pulling out all the big guns. Going to blitz the bastard, yeah?
使出全部解數 准備給這混蛋迎頭痛擊
What is it?
怎么了?
- I don't know if I should tell you. - Tell me what?
- 我不知道該不該告訴你 - 告訴我什么?
Liam Foyle confirmed defence counsel today.
Liam Foyle今天確認了辯護律師
Who is it?
是誰
I thought you were still on leave?
我以為你還在休假?
I am.
是在
I, erm, I sent you a card. I hope...
我 呃 給你寄了慰問卡片 希望...
You're defending him.
你擔任他的辯護律師
If you mean Liam Foyle, then yes.
如果你是指Liam Foyle 那么是的
Yes, you're correct.
你說的沒錯
Look, after everything that's happened, I mean...
聽著 發生這一切 我...
I know this must be very hard for you. I really do.
我知道對你的打擊一定很大 真的
Yeah.
是的
You know as well as I do, for good or bad...
你我都知道 無論好壞
What can I say?
我能怎么說呢
Everyone deserves a defence.
因為每個人都享有辯護的權利
That's right, Maggie.
是的 Maggie
That's right.
說的是
next time Foyle murdered Sandra Mullins.
下集預告 Foyle殺害了Sandra Mullins
- You need to know that. - You said otherwise in court.
- 你得知道這一點 - 你在法庭上可不是這么說的
Let that man in, you're risking everything.
讓他接近 會有致命危險
I mean it. Don't be alone.
我說的是真的 別獨自一人
It was today, the plea?
是今天開庭嗎
They should have called you.
他們應該告訴你的
- He got bail. - When was this?
- 他獲得保釋了 - 什么時候的事
This morning.
今天早上
Lawyers don't have an ounce of mercy in them.
那些律師沒有一絲一毫的同情心
They can be manipulative.
他們很會操縱人心
- Never said thank you. - Oh, you're welcome.
- 我還沒向你道謝 - 哦 客氣了
See you soon.
回頭見
When were you planning on telling me?
你打算什么時候告訴我?
I want a meeting with everyone tonight.
我今天要和所有人會面
Dad! Look out!
爸爸 小心
- Is he here? - They said he'd already left.
- 他在這里嗎 - 他們說他已經離開了
- Why didn't you call me? - Dad! Dad!
- 為什么不打電話給我 - 爸爸
Dad! Dad!
爸爸
Join our FRS/FRM and have fun! QQ Group No.  77207643/frzhaopin2@gmail.com
Join our FRS/FRM and have fun! QQ Group No.  77207643/frzhaopin2@gmail.com
www.1000fr.net presents
www.1000fr.net presents